[music]
[音乐]
Hello and welcome to this massive
您好，欢迎来到如此庞大的规模
open online course on JDK 8.
打开有关JDK 8的在线课程。
In this course we're going to be looking at some of the new features that have been
在本课程中，我们将研究一些新功能
included
包括在内
in JDK 8 and the Java programming language
在JDK 8和Java编程语言中
and Java libraries, which allow you to take a more functional approach
和Java库，这些库使您可以采用更实用的方法
when developing applications. This will use
在开发应用程序时。这将使用
Lambda expressions the streams API. My name is on Simon Ritter,
Lambda表达式 stream API。我叫西蒙·里特（Simon Ritter），
Java Technology Evangelist,
Java技术推广员，
and I will be guiding you through the 3 weekly lessons that we have
我将指导您完成我们的三个每周课程
for this course. The aim of this course
本课程。本课程的目的
is to give you an idea about how you can use
是给你一个关于如何使用的想法
Lambda expressions, so we'll talk about various aspects of those
Lambda表达式，所以我们将讨论这些表达式的各个方面
Lambda expressions in terms of the syntax; where you can use them; how you can use and so on.
Lambda表达式的语法；您可以在哪里使用它们；如何使用等。
Then we'll talk about the Streams API and how
然后，我们将讨论Streams API以及如何
they can use Lambda expressions extensively to give you a more
他们可以广泛使用Lambda表达式为您提供更多
functional style of
的函数式风格
programming using JDK 8. What this gives you
使用JDK 8进行编程
when you understand how to use these correctly, is a
当您了解如何正确使用它们时，
much better way of solving a lot of common problems
解决很多常见问题的更好方法
in terms of how we process data,
在我们如何处理数据方面，
how we process collections data. It gives you much more concise
我们如何处理收集数据。它使您更加简洁
more flexible way of doing that, so the code becomes
更灵活的方式，因此代码变为
easier to read, easier to understand, and easier to maintain.
更易于阅读，更易于理解和维护。
One the other big advantages in this is
另一个很大的优势是
the fact that you can now much more easily
您现在可以轻松得多的事实
take advantage of multiple core processors and,
利用多个核心处理器，并且
if your machine has more multiple processors, then
如果您的计算机具有更多的多个处理器，则
the parallel execution code could be made much, much simpler
并行执行代码可以变得非常简单
using this type of syntax.
使用这种类型的语法。
Let's start with lesson 1, and in this lesson
让我们从第1课开始，在本课中
we're going to look at Lambda expressions. The agenda for this lesson
我们将看一下Lambda表达式。本课程的议程
is firstly we'll start talking about why
首先，我们将开始谈论为什么
we need to add Lambda expressions to Java. Java is
我们需要向Java添加Lambda表达式。 Java是
twenty-years-old and we been very happily programming for those last 20
二十岁的时候，我们为过去20年的编程非常愉快
years, last
岁月
nineteen years since JDK 8 is about a year
自JDK 8至今已有19年了
since it was released, so we've been using them Java for
自发布以来，我们一直在使用Java
a good nineteen years without Lambda expressions, so why do we need to add
没有Lambda表达式的很好的19年，为什么我们需要添加
at this point in time?
在这个时间点？
We need to understand the syntax of
我们需要了解的语法
Lambda expressions, so we'll cover that in some detail and then
Lambda表达式，因此我们将对其进行详细介绍，然后
we'll look at places where you can actually use Lambda expressions
我们将研究可以实际使用Lambda表达式的地方
and this is, essentially, wherever you can use a
从本质上讲，这是您可以在哪里使用
function interface. So we'll describe what functional interfaces are,
功能界面。因此，我们将描述什么是功能接口，
their definition, how you use them and so on.
它们的定义，使用方式等。
We'll move from there
我们将从那里出发
to looking at some of the new functional interfaces that have been
看一些新的功能接口
included
包括在内
in the java.util.function package and these
在java.util.function包中，以及这些
are very relevant when we start talking about streams
当我们开始谈论流时，这是非常相关的
in lesson two because they are used extensively
在第二课中，因为它们被广泛使用
in conjunction with streams. One of the other things that we've included in JDK 8
与流结合。 JDK 8中包含的另一件事
around Lambda expressions
Lambda表达式周围
is a shorthand way of creating certain types of Lambda
是创建某些类型的Lambda的简便方法
expressions, where you're using just calls to a particular method
表达式，您只使用对特定方法的调用
or using a constructor, so these are method and constructor references
或使用构造函数，所以这些是方法和构造函数的引用
and we'll explain the three different situations we can use those and
我们将说明三种可以使用的不同情况
again the syntax and the way those work. There are some
再次说明语法和工作方式。有一些
quite, not complicated rules, but there are some rules that you need to
相当复杂的规则，但是您需要一些规则
understand
了解
about how you can reference variables from the surrounding scope
关于如何从周围的范围引用变量
in Lambda expression. We'll cover that in some detail,
在Lambda表达式中。我们将对此进行详细介绍，
we'll talk about what the rules are, how you can use things and also
我们将讨论规则是什么，如何使用事物以及
how the compiler can actually help you certain situations.
编译器如何实际帮助您解决某些情况。
In the last part of this lesson we'll look at some of the new methods that
在本课程的最后一部分，我们将介绍一些新方法
have been added to the existing
已经添加到现有的
JDK 8 libraries outside the streams API
流API之外的JDK 8库
where you can use Lambda expressions; some of the really useful things you
您可以在其中使用Lambda表达式；一些您真正有用的东西
can do
可以做
for collections and also for things like logging.
用于收集，也用于日志记录。
We'll start then with part one of Lesson one about
然后，我们从第一课的第一部分开始
why does Java need Lambda expressions? Now I mentioned
Java为什么需要Lambda表达式？现在我提到
that what this allows you to do is to simplify
这允许您做的是简化
how you can take advantage of multicore
如何利用多核
processors and multiple processors.
处理器和多个处理器。
If you look at the history of Java what you'll find is that right from the very
如果您看一下Java的历史，您会发现从一开始就是这样
beginning
开始
Java had the concept of
Java的概念是
being able to support multiple streams of execution,
能够支持多个执行流，
multiple threads of execution.
多执行线程。
In JDK 1.0 you had a java.lang.thread class,
在JDK 1.0中，您有一个java.lang.thread类，
which allows you to create a separate thread. You could define
它允许您创建一个单独的线程。您可以定义
through the use of something like a runnable what the code was
通过使用类似可运行的代码
you want to execute within that thread. That was great because it meant that it
您想在该线程中执行。那很棒，因为那意味着
was very simple
很简单
to create multiple threads that could do things potentially in parallel.
创建多个可以并行执行操作的线程。
The problem that we had with that
我们遇到的问题
was when you had several threads all which wanted to work together
是当您有多个线程想要一起工作时
if they were working separately that was no issue once you want threads to work
如果它们是分开工作的，一旦您希望线程工作就没问题了
together
一起
to share data and to be able to coordinate
共享数据并能够协调
their activities, to certain points in time
他们的活动，在某些时间点
then you quite restricted in what you can do with the thread.
那么您在使用该线程时会受到很大的限制。
There are essentially four methods in the thread class
线程类中基本上有四个方法
that allow you to do that, there is sleep, interrupt,
可以做到的，有睡眠，打扰，
wait and notify.
等待并通知。
Writing code that has multiple threads working together
编写具有多个线程协同工作的代码
just using those APIs is actually very difficult.
仅使用这些API实际上非常困难。
What we wanted to do was to simplify that.
我们想要做的就是简化它。
In JDK 5.0 we introduced
在JDK 5.0中，我们介绍了
the concurrency utilities (this was JSR 166,
并发实用程序（这是JSR 166，
Java specification request 166).
Java规范要求166）。
What this provided you with was quite a big
这为您提供了很大的帮助
toolbox of new classes
新类工具箱
and API's that made this coordination
和API进行了这种协调
of multiple threads simpler. We introduced
多个线程更简单。我们介绍了
the kind of concepts that people who've done multi-threaded programming in
进行过多线程编程的人所喜欢的那种概念
other languages on other platforms already used to.
已经在其他平台上使用的其他语言。
Things like a Semaphore class, things like new mutexes,
信号量类，新互斥量等
read/write locks, atomic operations; all of
读/写锁，原子操作；所有的
those types of things that people were familiar with and getting used to
人们熟悉并习惯的那些类型的事物
create better code in terms of multi-threading.
在多线程方面创建更好的代码。
In JDK 6
在JDK 6中
we had a few more advanced features things like Phasers which was just
我们有一些更高级的功能，例如相位器
another way of having
另一种拥有
multiple threads all working seem simultaneously
多个线程似乎同时工作
and then arriving at a particular point in time so they could deliver a particular set of
然后到达特定的时间点，以便他们可以提供一组特定的
results.
结果。
In JDK 7
在JDK 7中
we had another attempt at making life easier for writing
我们还尝试过使写作更轻松的生活
multi-threaded code and code that ran in parallel. We introduced
多线程代码和并行运行的代码。我们介绍了
the fork-join framework. What this gives you
fork-join框架。这给你什么
is the ability to take a single task which can be broken down into
是执行一项任务的能力，可以分解为
multiple sub tasks and have that happen recursively
多个子任务，并以递归方式进行
until you get to a small enough task that could be handled by single thread.
直到您完成可以由单线程处理的足够小的任务。
The framework takes care all creating a pool of threads to use,
该框架负责所有创建要使用的线程池，
it takes care all allocating various tasks to
照顾所有分配各种任务
the different queues associated with those
与那些相关的不同队列
threads and then it takes care of gathering all the results together once
线程，然后将所有结果收集在一起一次
the
的
queues have been processed and delivering the final result. So that was good,
队列已处理完毕并提供最终结果。这样很好
but it still had the drawback that it required quite a lot of
但是它仍然有缺点，它需要很多
boilerplate code to use that effectively.
样板代码可以有效地使用它。
For JDK 8
对于JDK 8
we sat down and thought, well we want to add more features, but we want to make it easier
我们坐下来想，好吧，我们想添加更多功能，但我们想让它更容易
still
仍然
for people to write parallel code. At this point we realized
为人们编写并行代码。至此，我们意识到
that we couldn't just add more APIs in classes to standard
我们不能只是在标准的类中添加更多的API
class libraries. In order to make life easier for developers,
类库。为了使开发人员的生活更轻松，
we had to make some changes to the language syntax that
我们必须对语言语法进行一些更改
we could then use in conjunction with new API's
然后，我们可以与新的API结合使用
to make this simpler. This is what
使它更简单。这是什么
the Lambda expression syntax and project Lambdas
Lambda表达式语法和项目Lambdas
is all about. So this is why we wanted to add Lambdas.
关于一切。这就是为什么我们要添加Lambda。
Primarily to make life easier for you as developers
主要是为了使开发人员的生活更轻松
to write parallel code that could work
编写可能有效的并行代码
in simple way.
以简单的方式。
Let's have a look act a sample piece of code
让我们看一下示例代码
and this is the kind code we were writing lot
这是我们写的那种代码
in Java. What we have here is
在Java中。我们在这里是
a collection of data, in this case it's a collection
数据的集合，在这种情况下，它是一个集合
of records about students who take exams over
关于参加考试的学生的记录
various years. What we want to extract from this information
多年。我们要从这些信息中提取什么
is what was the highest score
最高分数是多少
that any student got, who graduated
任何毕业的学生
in the year 2011. We can see here
在2011年。我们可以在这里看到
do we've got fairly simple piece of code. What I've done
我们有一段相当简单的代码吗？我做了什么
is I've got my collection of students and then
是我收集了学生，然后
I create a variable called highest score. I've assigned that an initial value of zero,
我创建一个变量称为最高分。我已将初始值指定为零，
so that we can update that as we find higher scores.
这样我们可以在找到更高分数时进行更新。
Then we use the
然后我们使用
very common way we do things in Java which is we iterate.
我们在Java中做事的一种非常普遍的方式是迭代。
Java is an imperative language,
Java是命令式语言，
that means that we have sequences of commands,
这意味着我们有一系列命令，
which can manipulate variables
可以操纵变量
to update things and process data,
更新事物和处理数据，
as we want it. In this case we want to iterate
如我们所愿。在这种情况下，我们要迭代
over the collection of students so we look at each student in turn
收集学生的资料，因此我们依次查看每个学生
looking at their graduation year and looking at their score.
看他们的毕业年份，看他们的分数。
We use the more modern foreach syntax for this loop.
对于此循环，我们使用更现代的foreach语法。
This in itself hides some of the details
这本身隐藏了一些细节
because in this case what we'll actually have to do
因为在这种情况下，我们实际上必须要做的是
is to extract the iterator from the collection students
是从集合学生中提取迭代器
and then we're going to have to repeatedly get
然后我们将不得不反复获得
elements from that iterator so we actually moved through the collection
该迭代器中的元素，因此我们实际上遍历了集合
until there are no more elements left.
直到没有更多的元素了。
The syntax of that for statement is actually a bit more complicated
for语句的语法实际上有点复杂
we just using shorthand which simplifies it in terms of our
我们只是使用速记来简化我们的操作
code.
码。
As we move through the collection of students we look at each record
当我们浏览学生的集合时，我们会查看每条记录
we can compare the graduation year
我们可以比较毕业年份
of that student to 2011. If they graduated in that year, which is
的学生到2011年的百分比。如果他们当年毕业，
the year we're interested in, then we look at their score.
我们感兴趣的年份，然后看看他们的得分。
We compare the score of that student against out current highest score.
我们将该学生的分数与当前的最高分数进行比较。
If the student has a higher score than
如果学生的分数高于
that number, then we assign the
该数字，然后我们分配
value of our highest score, the value we're recording
我们最高分的价值，我们正在记录的价值
to whatever that student got in their exam.
不管那个学生参加考试。
At the end of this, what we're going to have
最后，我们将要拥有的
is the highest score any student got in the year 2011.
是所有学生在2011年获得的最高分。
We've solved the problem. There is absolutely nothing wrong
我们已经解决了问题。绝对没有错
functionally with what we doing in this code.
在功能上与我们在这段代码中所做的一样。
The functionality works perfectly. The problem
该功能运行完美。问题
is in terms of how we would want to
就我们想如何
process that if we want to take advantage of multiple cores and multiple
如果我们想利用多个核心和多个优势
processors.
处理器。
By having our loop
通过循环
here what we're doing is we're controlling iteration.
在这里，我们正在控制迭代。
We're defining through our loop the order
我们通过循环定义顺序
in which the elements of that collection are going to be processed.
其中将处理该集合的元素。
That means that we in effect have a contract between
这意味着我们实际上在
our code and the compiler and the runtime that states the order they will be
我们的代码，编译器以及说明它们顺序的运行时
processed.
处理。
Although it doesn't actually matter in this case
虽然在这种情况下实际上并不重要
if we were doing other things which which did require
如果我们在做其他需要做的事情
that order to be maintained we couldn't break it up into parallel operations
保持秩序，我们无法将其分解为并行操作
because breaking it up and parallel operations we would introduce
因为将其分解和并行操作，我们将介绍
non-deterministic behaviour because different threads could execute at different
非确定性行为，因为不同的线程可以在不同的位置执行
times, they could be looking at different pieces data and so we may not always get
有时，他们可能正在查看不同的碎片数据，因此我们可能不会总是得到
the same result.
同样的结果。
We have control over the situation
我们可以控制局势
which means that out code is inherently serial. We start at the beginning of the
这意味着输出代码本质上是串行的。我们从
collection and
收集和
we move to the end to the collection.
我们移到集合的末尾。
The other problem we have is even if we were to
我们面临的另一个问题是，即使我们要
rewrite our loop and trying to avoid using loop explicitly
重写我们的循环，并尝试避免显式使用循环
we still have a variable highestScore
我们还有一个变量highScore
and this is mutable state.
这是可变状态。
Having a variable that we can change and if we would have multiple threads
拥有一个可以更改的变量以及是否有多个线程
we would still have problems because it's not thread-safe
我们仍然会遇到问题，因为它不是线程安全的
multiple threads could be updating that variable at the same
多个线程可能会同时更新该变量
time and overwrite the changes which are made by other threads.
时间并覆盖其他线程所做的更改。
We would need to introduce locking to prevent multiple threads from accessing
我们将需要引入锁定以防止多个线程访问
it
它
at the same time and that would add more work to our
同时，这将为我们增加更多的工作
application code. Right now we have good works but it's not
应用程序代码。现在我们有很好的作品，但是还没有
good in terms multi-threading and parallel execution.
在多线程和并行执行方面表现出色。
Let's take the same code
让我们采用相同的代码
and rewrite its using a more functional approach.
并使用更实用的方法重写它。
Now we're going to talk about functional programming
现在我们要讨论函数式编程
a lot more in lesson two, at the beginning of that lesson, but for now you can think
在第二课中，在该课的开始，还有很多很多，但是现在您可以考虑
of
的
a more functional approach as being simply the ability to chain together
一种更实用的方法，就是简单地链接在一起的能力
method calls to have things execute one after the other.
方法调用使事情一个接一个地执行。
Now what we're doing is we're taking a collection of students
现在我们正在做的是招收一批学生
and not using an explicit loop. Now we're passing in the collection of students
而不使用显式循环。现在我们传递学生的集合
records to a filter method. The filter method
记录到过滤方法。过滤方式
is told how to do filtering
被告知如何进行过滤
using a Predicate interface. The Predicate interface
使用谓词接口。谓词接口
has a single method and we use an anonymous inner class
有一个方法，我们使用一个匿名内部类
to define what that method is going to do.
定义该方法将要执行的操作。
In this case it's a method called op, that takes a student as a parameter and
在这种情况下，这是一个称为op的方法，该方法将一个学生作为参数，
returns boolean. We compare the graduation year
返回布尔值。我们比较毕业年份
of a student to 2011. The
的学生到2011年。
output of the filter method will be a subset of
过滤器方法的输出将是
all the students that we have to start with, which will
我们必须开始的所有学生
only be the students who graduated in the year 2011.
仅是2011年毕业的学生。
We take that subset of data and we pass it to another method,
我们采用该数据子集并将其传递给另一种方法，
this case called map, which uses another
这种情况称为地图，它使用另一个
anonymous inner class
匿名内部阶级
called Mapper to determine
叫Mapper确定
how to actually do that mapping, and in this case
如何实际执行该映射，在这种情况下
it has a single method called extract, takes a student, s,
它有一个称为提取的单一方法，需要一个学生s，
as parameter and returns a double. For this
作为参数并返回一个double。为了这
we take the collection of students who graduated in 2011
我们收集了2011年毕业的学生
and we convert that into collection of records
然后将其转换为记录集合
of the scores of those students. At the end of the map
这些学生的分数。在地图的尽头
we have all the scores of the students who graduated in 2011.
我们拥有2011年毕业学生的所有分数。
We pass that collection of data
我们通过数据收集
into what is in effect a reduce operation, but it's a special form
归结为实际上的归约运算，但这是一种特殊形式
of reduce, which is max. It takes all these
的减少，最大值所有这些
double values and looks at them and detemines which
将值加倍并查看它们并确定
is the highest value and we return that result as
是最高值，我们将结果返回为
our end result. This is good.
我们的最终结果。很好
This is much better in terms of looking at how we can do parallel
就我们如何并行执行而言，这要好得多
processing,
处理
how we can use those multicore, multi CPU machines.
我们如何使用这些多核，多CPU机器。
We don't have explicit iteration, there's no
我们没有明确的迭代，也没有
loop there, so the iteration can be handled
在那里循环，因此可以处理迭代
internally within the filter or the map with max method.
在内部使用max方法在过滤器或地图中。
That means that if the library code wants to do that in parallel
这意味着如果库代码想要并行执行此操作
we haven't forced, by defining filter and map methods,
通过定义过滤器和映射方法，我们并没有强迫，
we haven't forced an order of execution on that.
我们并没有为此强制执行命令。
Now we're not doing it inherently serially,
现在我们不是天生就按顺序进行，
we can do it in parallel if we want to. We can also
如果需要，我们可以并行进行。我们也可以
apply some other optimizations so that, if we wanted to, we could do lazy
应用一些其他优化，以便我们愿意的话
evaluation,
评估，
we could merge together the filtering and the mapping,
我们可以将过滤和映射合并在一起，
so we did them is a combined operation on each element as it comes through the
因此，当它们通过
set of method calls. Because we don't have
方法调用集。因为我们没有
a variable which we're updating explicitly here
我们将在此处明确更新的变量
we're also thread safe. The client logic, what we're looking at here
我们也是线程安全的。客户逻辑，我们在这里看
is stateless. The result is generated internally,
是无国籍的。结果是在内部生成的
so we don't have to worry about the state being modified
所以我们不必担心状态被修改
in our
在我们的
code. That's great. What's the
码。那很棒。那是什么
downside? Well, the downside is
缺点？不好的是
is very simple; its just plain ugly.
很简单它只是丑陋的。
What I've done to illustrate that is I've put some the code in red
为了说明这一点，我将一些代码标记为红色
and most code in black. The code that's in red
和大多数黑色代码。红色代码
is actually what we're really interested in. We've got a collection of students, we're after the
实际上是我们真正感兴趣的。我们有很多学生，我们追求
highest score,
最高分
we want to filter, we want to test against the graduation year being
我们要过滤，我们要针对毕业年份进行测试
2011. We want to map, we want to get the score, we want to max.
2011。我们想作图，我们要获得比分，我们要达到最高。
All the rest of it, the fact we're using a predicate of
所有其他情况，我们使用的是谓词
type student, which has a method called op,
类型的学生，有一种称为op的方法，
returning a boolean, and so on, is boilerplat code. We just
返回布尔值，依此类推，是锅炉代码。我们刚刚
really don't want to have that. That is what
真的不想拥有那个。那是什么
Lambda expressions are all about; how we can simplify
Lambda表达式是关于；我们如何简化
this kind of code in order to make it
这种代码以使其成为
easier to understand. If we rewrite
更容易理解。如果我们重写
the code that we had using Lambda expressions
使用Lambda表达式的代码
we can see that, suddenly, it becomes much
我们可以看到突然之间
simpler. Now what we're saying in case of the filter,
更简单。现在我们要说的是过滤器
we need to define this single method called op that
我们需要定义一个称为op的单一方法
we have in our Predicate. You can think about of a Lambda expression at this
我们在谓词中。您可以在此考虑Lambda表达式
point in time
时间点
as being like a method, but its is not really a method.
就像是一种方法，但实际上并不是一种方法。
I'll explain that as we go through other parts of the lesson. For now think of it being like
在本课程的其他部分中，我将对此进行解释。现在想想就像
a method. It's like the method we saw in the anonymous inner class
一个方法。就像我们在匿名内部类中看到的方法
in the previous slide. For filter we have
在上一张幻灯片中。对于过滤器，我们有
method, who's parameter in this case student s;
方法，在这种情况下，谁是学生的参数；
that's the left hand side of the arrow. The body of the method
那是箭头的左侧。方法的主体
is to return whether the graduation year
是否返回毕业年份
is 2011 or not. Immediately, you can see that
是不是2011年。立刻，您可以看到
this this is not like a method as we used to
这不像我们以前使用的方法
because is no explicit return statement. The compiler
因为没有明确的return语句。编译器
will infer from the fact that we're comparing graduation year
将从我们正在比较毕业年份的事实中推断出来
to 2011 that the result is going to be a boolean. Similarly,
到2011年，结果将是布尔值。同样，
when we look at the map method we're passing in a Lambda expression.
当我们查看map方法时，我们传入的是Lambda表达式。
The left hand side of the arrow is the parameters, student s,
箭头的左侧是参数s，
the right hand side is the body, which simply returns
右侧是身体，只是返回
the score of that student and the compiler will infer that's a
该学生和编译器的分数将推断出这是一个
double based on the fact that the signature of getScore
基于getScore签名的事实加倍
is to return a double. max doesn't require a
是要返回双倍。最高不需要
Lambda expression, so it just turns the maximum value.
Lambda表达式，因此它只是变成最大值。
This gives us something that is
这给了我们一些东西
much more readable, so it's more abstract in terms the approach that we take,
更具可读性，因此我们采用的方法更加抽象，
and because it's much simpler in terms the the code,
而且因为它在代码方面要简单得多，
much less code that we have to look at, it's much less error-prone.
我们所要查看的代码少得多，错误也少得多。
We don't have to worry about do we get the type to the method right, do we get the
我们不必担心我们将类型正确设置为方法，是否会获得
type of
类型
generic parameter right. All of those things
通用参数权限。所有这些东西
are done for us by the compiler, so we have a much simpler way of
由编译器为我们完成，所以我们有一种更简单的方法
looking at the code when we want to do this kind of thing.
当我们想做这种事情的时候看一下代码。
To summarize section one of this lesson,
总结本课的第一节，
we needed changes to the Java language not just to the API's,
我们需要对Java语言进行更改，而不仅仅是对API进行更改，
so that we could simplify how we could deal
这样我们就可以简化交易方式
with parallel coding. What
与并行编码。什么
Lambda expressions really gives us is
Lambda表达式真正给我们的是
a very simple way now to be able to pass
现在可以通过的非常简单的方法
behaviour as a parameter to a method.
行为作为方法的参数。
We've had that in the past in terms of anonymous inner classes, but
过去在匿名内部类方面有过
because of this rather verbose syntax
由于这种相当冗长的语法
it's always been very difficult to use that effectively. Now we have a 00:21:14,080 --&gt; 00:21:15,010 simple way
一直很难有效地使用它。现在我们有了一个350 00：21：14,080-&gt; 00：21：15,010的简单方法
to past behavior as a parameter as well as values,
将过去的行为作为参数和值，
because most the time we pass values as parameters.
因为大多数时候我们将值作为参数传递。
Now we can pass behavior as well and we can also sign behavior
现在我们也可以传递行为，也可以对行为进行签名
to a variable if we want to. That
如果需要的话，将其设置为变量。那
is the end of part 1 of this
是第1部分的结尾
lesson.
课。